insiderworkshops.com 2011-10-06

# Privacy | Insider Workshops

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or other details. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
To process transactions  
To send periodic emails

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. Payments are taken by a 3rd-party payment solution such as Paypal and we do not store or use your credit card information. We can also process credit card information by phone, email or fax. Our company does not store any financial details.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on 15th Feb 2011
